Andrew Bielecki

ambielecki@gmail.com | www.andrewbielecki.me | 5 Island Hill Ave #302, Malden, MA 02148

Summary

I spent ten years after graduating university in the Biotechnology field working in Biochemistry setting up screening assays for small molecule enzymatic inhibitors. This allowed me to grow skills in robotics programming, data analysis and general problem solving. I am now looking to move in computer programming / database management to leverage those skills along with additional coursework through the Web Technologies Certificate at Harvard Extension School.

Experience

Teaching Assistant, Harvard Extension School CSCI E-15, Cambridge, MA, Part Time	Spring 2016
This course focuses on developing Dynamic Web Applications with the Laravel PHP framework	
Webmaster, Malden Little League, www.maldenlittleleague.org	2016
Designed and maintain site using the Laravel Framework and MySQL database	
Research Investigator, Millennium Pharmaceuticals, Cambridge, MA, Full Time	2002-2011
Research Associate, Millennium Pharmaceuticals, Cambridge, MA, Full Time	2001-2002
Research Associate, BASF, Worcester, MA, Full Time	2000-2001

Skills

Experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, Oracle, PHP, Laravel Framework

Publications

<u>Identification of a regulatory autophosphorylation site in the serine-threonine kinase RIP2</u>.

DorschM, Wang A, Cheng H, Lu C, Bielecki A, Charron K, Clauser K, Ren H, Polakiewicz RD, Parsons T, Li P, Ocain T, Xu Y.

Cell Signal. 2006 Dec; 18(12):2223-9. Epub 2006 May 22.

A selective small molecule IkappaB Kinase beta inhibitor blocks nuclear factor kappaB-mediated inflammatory reponses in human fibroblast-like synoviocytes, chondrocytes, and mast cells.

Wen D, Nong Y, Morgan JG, Gangurde P, Bielecki A, Dasilva J, Keaveney M, Cheng H, Fraser C, Schopf L, Hepperle M, Harriman G, Jaffee BD, Ocain TD, Xu Y.

J Pharmacol Exp Ther. 2006 Jun; 317(3);998-1001. Epub 2006 Mar 8.

Education

Degree Candidate, Master of Liberal Arts, Information Technology, Harvard University Extension	2016
School, Cambridge, MA	
Web Technologies Certificate, Harvard University Extension School	2016
Bachelor of Arts, Biochemistry, Brandeis University, Waltham, MA	1996-2000

2016

Community Service

Board of Directors, Information Officer, Malden Little League, Malden, MA

Designed and maintain the Malden Little League website (www.maledenlittleleague.org) and manage the league's online presence.